A Guide to the Harry Flood Byrd, Sr. Papers
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series IV: Miscellaneous Topics
  - F. Speeches and Statements
    - 2. Harry Flood Byrd's Speeches
      - Virginia Bankers Conference, Charlottesville, Va., 1949 September 9 (Box Box 369)
      - Nomination of Carl A. Ilgenfritz, 1949 September 16 (Box Box 369)
      - Sales Executive Club, Richmond, Virginia, 1949 September 19 (Box Box 369)
      - Senate - Military Arms Program, 1949 September 21 (Box Box 369)
      - National Association of Insurance Agents, Chicago, Ill., 1949 September 22 (Box Box 369)
      - Chamber of Commerce, Richmond, Virginia, 1949 September 29 (Box Box 369)
      - Remarks in regard to the nomination of Leland Olds, 1949 October 7 (Box Box 369)
      - American Hardware Manufacturers Association and the National Wholesale Hardware Association, Atlantic City, N.J., 1949 October 12 (Box Box 369)
      - National Wholesale Druggists Association in Atlantic City, N. J., 1949 October 12 (Box Box 369)
      - Remarks on Government's Financial Situation, 1949 October 15 (Box Box 369)
      - National Retail Farm Equipment Association, Washington, D.C., 1949 October 19 (Box Box 369)
      - Essex Club Luncheon, Newark, N. J., 1949 October 27 (Box Box 369)
      - Testimonial Dinner honoring Honorable Albert W. Hawkes, East Orange, N. J., 1949 October 27 (Box Box 369)
      - Abstract of speech before A.A.A., in Cleveland, Ohio, 1949 November 1 (Box Box 369)
      - Abstract of speech before Commercial Club, Chicago, Ill., 1949 November 2 (Box Box 369)
      - Board of Underwriters, Chicago, Ill., 1949 November 22 (Box Box 369)
      - Fiscal Budget, 1949 (Box Box 369)
      - Budget, 1950 January 9 (Box Box 370)
      - Southern States Industrial Council's, Atlanta, Georgia, 1950 January 12 (Box Box 370)
      - Radio interview with Mr. Bryan, Atlanta, Ga., 1950 January 12 (Box Box 370)
      - Junior Chamber of Commerce, Roanoke, Virginia, 1950 January 14 (Box Box 370)
      - Wholesale Dry Goods Institute, New York, 1950 January 16 (Box Box 370)
      - Chamber of Commerce, Charleston, S. C., 1950 January 20 (Box Box 370)
      - Radio Transcription for Charles Parmer, 1950 January 23 (Box Box 370)
      - National Industrial Conference Board, New York, 1950 January 26 (Box Box 370)
      - Nurseryman's Association, Richmond, Virginia, 1950 January 30 (Box Box 370)
      - Senate - Coal Strike, 1950 January 30 (Box Box 370)
      - Remarks in the Senate - Government Financing and Spending, 1950 February 6 (Box Box 370)
      - National Automobile Dealers Association, Atlantic City, N. J., 1950 February 8 (Box Box 370)
      - Chamber of Commerce, Danville, Virginia, 1950 February 17 (Box Box 370)
      - Chamber of Commerce, New Haven, Conn., 1950 February 20 (Box Box 370)
      - Senator Humphrey attacking Senator Byrd's Joint Committee on Reduction of Fed. Exp., 1950 February 24 (Box Box 370)
      - Radio Transcription prepared for America's Future, Inc. and Mr. Earl Harding, 1950 February 25 (Box Box 370)
      - National Small Business Men's Association, Hotel Statler, Washington, D.C., 1950 March 1 (Box Box 370)
      - Reply to Senator Humphrey, 1950 March 2 (Box Box 370)
      - North Carolina Citizens Association, Raleigh, N. C., 1950 March 15 (Box Box 370)
      - The Rivers and Harbors Bill, 1950 April 17 (Box Box 370)
      - N.A.M. Luncheon, Washington, D. C., 1950 April 21 (Box Box 370)
      - American Academy of Political Science, Hotel Astor, New York, 1950 April 26 (Box Box 370)
      - Senate - Foreign Aid, 1950 May 5 (Box Box 370)
      - Delta Council, Cleveland, Miss., 1950 May 9 (Box Box 370)
      - Gridiron Dinner, Washington, D. C., 1950 May 13 (Box Box 370)
      - Maryland Chapter of University of Virginia Alumni, Baltimore, Maryland, 1950 May 18 (Box Box 370)
      - University of South Carolina, Columbia, S.C., 1950 June 5 (Box Box 370)
      - Budget Deficit, 1950 June 28 (Box Box 370)
      - Korean situation, 1950 June 30 (Box Box 370)
      - Omnibus Appropriation bill, 1950 July 11 (Box Box 371)
      - Senate - Response to Senator Humphrey's attack on the Committee., 1950 July 11 (Box Box 371)
      - Single Appropriation Bill, 1950 July 14 (Box Box 371)
      - Nurserymen's Association, Statler Hotel, Washington, D. C., 1950 July 20 (Box Box 371)
      - Baruch Control Proposals, 1950 July 31 (Box Box 371)
      - Introducing amendment to limit the powers of the President to 1 year. Amendment A to S 3936, 1950 July 31 (Box Box 371)
      - Amendment to Appropriation Bill, 1950 July 31 (Box Box 371)
      - Letter from Senator Byrd and Editorial from Wall Street Journal re: Reduction Nondefense Budget, 1950 August 1 (Box Box 371)
      - Remarks re: Douglas Amendment to Appropriation Bill, 1950 August 1 (Box Box 371)
      - Introducing amendment to reduce non military appropriations by ten per cent, 1950 August 4 (Box Box 371)
      - Radio Transcript on our intelligence service in Korea, 1950 August 7 (Box Box 371)
      - The International Apple Association, Washington, D. C., 1950 August 8 (Box Box 371)
      - Nomination of Martin A. Hutchinson, 1950 August 9 (Box Box 371)
      - Remarks offering an Amendment to the Appropriation Bill, 1950 August 9 (Box Box 371)
      - Orchard Picnic, Berryville, Virginia, 1950 August 12 (Box Box 371)
      - American Legion, Alexandria, Virginia, 1950 August 18 (Box Box 371)
      - Senate - On the pending control bill, 1950 August 18 (Box Box 371)
      - Senate - On the One-Appropriation Bill, 1950 August 28 (Box Box 371)
      - Senate - In regard to H. Res. 87, 1950 August 31 (Box Box 371)
      - Annual Field Day at Ivy Hill, Lynchburg, Va., 1950 September 9 (Box Box 371)
      - National Tax Association, Pittsburgh, Pa., 1950 September 13 (Box Box 371)
      - Draft of remarks on the Panama Canal Question, 1950 September 13 (Box Box 371)
      - Senate - Appointment of General George Marshall as Secretary of Defense, 1950 September 16 (Box Box 371)
      - Remarks regarding appointment of Honorable Stephen E. Rice as Judge on the Tax Court of the United States, 1950 September 23 (Box Box 371)
      - Virginia Forum of the Chamber of Commerce, Richmond, Virginia, 1950 September 28 (Box Box 371)
      - National Association of Securities Traders, Virginia Beach, Virginia, 1950 September 30 (Box Box 371)
      - V. M. I., Lexington, Virginia, 1950 October 12 (Box Box 371)
      - Award to Senator Byrd by American Association of Credit Men in New York, 1950 October 20 (Box Box 371)
      - National Association of Ice Industries, Chicago, Ill., 1950 November 1 (Box Box 371)
      - Ohio State Chamber of Commerce, Columbus, Ohio, 1950 November 1 (Box Box 371)
      - Youngstown Chamber of Commerce, Youngstown, Ohio, 1950 November 14 (Box Box 371)
      - Virginia Forests, Inc., Richmond, Virginia, 1950 November 28 (Box Box 371)
      - Senate - On Statehood for Alaska, 1950 November 30 (Box Box 371)
      - Suffolk, Virginia, 1950 December 5 (Box Box 371)
      - Women's Club, Culpeper, Virginia, 1950 December 11 (Box Box 371)
      - Senate - On the nomination of Anna M. Rosenberg for Assist. Secretary of Defense, 1950 December 21 (Box Box 371)
      - Letter to the President, 1950 December 22 (Box Box 371)
      - Norfolk, Virginia, 1951 January 20 (Box Box 372)
      - Council of State Chambers, Carlton Hotel, Washington, D. C., 1951 January 26 (Box Box 372)
      - Potomac States Bakers Association, Baltimore, Md., 1951 January 29 (Box Box 372)
      - Arlington Chamber of Commerce, Airport, Arlington, Virginia, 1951 February 1 (Box Box 372)
      - Senate - Analysis of the Budget, 1951 February 5 (Box Box 372)
      - Senate - "Quickie" tax bills, 1951 February 8 (Box Box 372)
      - National Canners Association, Chicago, Ill., 1951 February 18 (Box Box 372)
      - Fredericksburg Chamber of Commerce, Fredericksburg, Virginia, 1951 February 22 (Box Box 372)
      - Commercial Club, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1951 February 23 (Box Box 372)
      - Remarks in the Senate on H.R. 1 and H.R. 1001, 1951 February 26 (Box Box 372)
      - Pennsylvania Manufacturers Association, Philadelphia, Pa., 1951 February 27 (Box Box 372)
      - Senate - Drafting of 18 year olds, 1951 March 5 (Box Box 372)
      - Remarks in the Senate on Universal Military Training Bill, 1951 March 9 (Box Box 372)
      - Remarks in the Senate on abolishing the R.F.C., 1951 March 14 (Box Box 372)
      - Springfield, Ohio, 1951 March 27 (Box Box 372)
      - New York Southern Society, New York, 1951 April 11 (Box Box 372)
      - D.A R., Washington, D. C., 1951 April 17 (Box Box 372)
      - Remarks in Senate - Consolidated General Appropriation Bill. (Folder empty when processed), 1951 April 17 (Box Box 372)
      - National Coal Association in New York, 1951 April 20 (Box Box 372)
      - Board of Trade, New York, 1951 April 20 (Box Box 372)
      - National Editorial Association, New York, 1951 April 20 (Box Box 372)
      - Dispersal Plan, 1951 April 23 (Box Box 372)
      - Virginia Federation of Womens Clubs, Washington, D. C., 1951 April 24 (Box Box 372)
      - Senate - RFC, 1951 April 30 (Box Box 372)
      - Senate - RFC, including letter from Hon. Jesse Jones, 1951 May 1 (Box Box 372)
      - U. S. Chamber of Commerce, Washington, D. C., 1951 May 1 (Box Box 372)
      - Armed Forces Day Observance, Newport News, Va., 1951 May 18 (Box Box 372)
      - Detroit Economic Club, Detroit, Mich., 1951 May 28 (Box Box 372)
      - South Carolina Bar Association, Greenville, S.C., 1951 June 8 (Box Box 372)
      - Tribute to George Mason, Richmond, Virginia, 1951 June 12 (Box Box 372)
      - Remarks in the Senate on appropriations for Information Specialists. (Folder empty when processed), 1951 June 19 and June 20 (Box Box 372)
      - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, Atlanta, Ga., 1951 June 25 (Box Box 373)
      - Remarks in the Senate on Appropriations, 1951 August 15 (Box Box 373)
      - Remarks on Amendment of Sec. 3121 of the Internal Revenue Code. S.J. Res. 97, 1951 September 7 (Box Box 373)
      - Remarks on Amendment to Defense Appropriations, particularly abuses by the Air Force, 1951 September 12 (Box Box 373)
      - Launderers and Cleaners, Old Point Comfort, Va, 1951 September 18 (Box Box 373)
      - Anniversary of Jefferson County, West Virginia, 1951 September 22 (Box Box 373)
      - Omaha, Neb. (Not delivered), 1951 October 12 (Box Box 373)
      - Dedicating Pollock Knob, Skyland, 1951 October 14 (Box Box 373)
      - Dallas County Farm Bureau, Selma, Ala., 1951 November 1 (Box Box 373)
      - Richmond Chamber of Commerce, Richmond, Va., 1951 November 8 (Box Box 373)
      - Tidewater Wholesale Food Dealers Association, Cavalier Hotel, Virginia Beach, Virginia, 1951 November 10 (Box Box 373)
      - American Medical Association, Los Angeles, Calif., 1951 December 5 (Box Box 373)
      - American Farm Bureau, Chicago, Ill., 1951 December 12 (Box Box 373)
      - Manion Press Release, [1951?] (Box Box 373)
      - Business Outlook Conference, Chattanooga, Tenn., 1952 January 18 (Box Box 373)
      - Virginia Dairy Products Association, Roanoke, Virginia. (Not delivered), 1952 January 22 (Box Box 373)
      - Chamber of Commerce, Staunton, Virginia, 1952 January 29 (Box Box 373)
      - Northeastern Retail Lumbermens Association, New York, 1952 January 31 (Box Box 373)
      - Mayors and other officials at Old Point Comfort, Virginia, 1952 February 1 (Box Box 373)
      - Chicago Dental Society, Chicago, Ill., 1952 February 4 (Box Box 374)
      - Budget, 1952 February 14 (Box Box 374)
      - University of Virginia Alumni Association, Washington, D. C., 1952 February 19 (Box Box 374)
      - American Paper and Pulp Association, New York, 1952 February 21 (Box Box 374)
      - The Rotary Club, Salisbury, Md., 1952 February 28 (Box Box 374)
      - Waynesboro, Virginia, 1952 March 17 (Box Box 374)
      - Lehigh Valley Cooperative Farmers, Allentown, Pa. (Not delivered), 1952 March 20 (Box Box 374)
      - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, Richmond, Virginia, 1952 April 17 (Box Box 374)
      - Senate - R.F.C. Bill, 1952 April 22 and 23 (Box Box 374)
      - American Newspaper Publishers Association, New York City, 1952 April 24 (Box Box 374)
      - Publicity Amendment - Senate Floor, 1952 April 29 (Box Box 374)
      - National Industrial Conference Board, New York, 1952 May 15 (Box Box 374)
      - Convention of State Treasurers, Richmond, Virginia, 1952 May 16 (Box Box 374)
      - American Cotton Manufacturers Association, Atlantic City, N. J., 1952 May 17 (Box Box 374)
      - Opening of Monroe Calculating Machine Company, Bristol, Virginia, 1952 May 19 (Box Box 374)
      - Honoring Gardner L. Boothe, Alexandria, Va., 1952 May 22 (Box Box 374)
      - Virginia Seedsmen Association, Winchester, Va., 1952 May 23 (Box Box 374)
      - Fireman's Day, Cheriton, Virginia, 1952 May 28 (Box Box 374)
      - Accomac, Virginia, 1952 May 28 (Box Box 374)
      - Suffolk, Virginia, 1952 May 30 (Box Box 374)
      - Virginia Alumni Association, Richmond, Va., 1952 June 3 (Box Box 375)
      - National Holstein Convention, Roanoke, Va., 1952 June 3 (Box Box 375)
      - Remarks in the Senate on Senator's Amendment to request the President to use the Taft-Hartley Act in the Steel Strike. (Folder empty when processed), 1952 June 5 (Box Box 375)
      - Fluvanna Farm Bureau, Carysbrook, Virginia, 1952 June 6 (Box Box 375)
      - Honoring Congressman Howard W. Smith, Belle Haven Country Club, Fairfax, Virginia, 1952 June 11 (Box Box 375)
      - Orange, Virginia, 1952 June 12 (Box Box 375)
      - Wytheville, Virginia, 1952 June 13 (Box Box 375)
      - Bland, Virginia, 1952 June 13 (Box Box 375)
      - Marion, Virginia, 1952 June 13 (Box Box 375)
      - Richlands, Virginia, 1952 June 14 (Box Box 375)
      - Pulaski, Virginia, 1952 June 14 (Box Box 375)
      - Tea at the home of Mrs. Harry K. Green, 1952 June 15 (Box Box 375)
      - Dinwiddie, Virginia, 1952 June 17 (Box Box 375)
      - Chatham, Virginia. (Farm Policy), 1952 June 19 (Box Box 375)
      - American Plant Food Council, Hot Springs, Va., 1952 June 21 (Box Box 375)
      - Bedford, Virginia, 1952 June 22 (Box Box 375)
      - Reply to W. Averell Harriman's radio broadcast to Virginia, 1952 June 25 (Box Box 375)
      - Institute of Public Affairs, University of Virginia, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1952 June 26 (Box Box 375)
      - Front Royal, Virginia, 1952 June 27 (Box Box 375)
      - Chesterfield Court House, Virginia, 1952 June 28 (Box Box 375)
      - Seaway and Labor, Hampton Roads, Virginia, 1952 June 30 (Box Box 375)
      - Norfolk, Virginia, 1952 June 30 (Box Box 375)
      - Military in Tidewater Area, 1952 June (Box Box 375)
      - Fairfax, Virginia. (Campaign), 1952 July 2 (Box Box 376)
      - Radio transcription of views on Labor, 1952 July 8 (Box Box 376)
      - Radio broadcast to the Farmers. (Campaign), 1952 July 9 (Box Box 376)
      - Telecast - Swanson Junior High School, Arlington, Virginia, 1952 July 9 (Box Box 376)
      - Lynchburg, Virginia, 1952 July 11 (Box Box 376)
      - Loyal Order of Moose, Harrisonburg, Virginia, 1952 July 13 (Box Box 376)
      - Senate - On the passing of Senator Willis Smith, 1953 July 1 (Box Box 376)
      - Remarks - Convention of the Blind, Washington, D. C., 1953 July 16 (Box Box 376)
      - Discussion in the Senate on the liquidation of the RFC., 1953 July 20 (Box Box 376)
      - Remarks in the Senate - Defense Appropriation Bill, 1953 July 22 (Box Box 376)
      - Remarks on the appointment of Admiral Wm. M. Fechteler, Com.in-Chief of the Allied Forces in Southern Europe, 1953 July 24 (Box Box 376)
      - Proposed increase in debt limit, 1953 July 29 (Box Box 376)
      - Remarks in the Senate relative to supplemental appropriation. (HR 6200), 1953 July 30 (Box Box 376)
      - Remarks in the Senate on the passing of Senator Taft, 1953 July 31 (Box Box 376)
      - Senate - National debt ceiling, 1953 August 3 (Box Box 376)
      - Remarks at Massanetta Bible Conference, 1953 August 28 (Box Box 376)
      - Transcription honoring Senator Pat McCarran, 1953 September 1 (Box Box 376)
      - Radio Speech from Winchester in the gubernatorial campaign, 1953 October 23 (Box Box 376)
      - Remarks at Newport News, Virginia welcoming the Pan American Oil Company, 1953 October 26 (Box Box 376)
      - Woodstock, Virginia during gubernatorial campaign, 1953 October 28 (Box Box 376)
      - Richmond Society of Financial Analysts, 1953 October 29 (Box Box 376)
      - W.I.N.C. Winchester, Virginia. Gubernatorial Campaign, 1953 November 2 (Box Box 376)
      - Rotary Club, Winchester, Virginia, 1953 December 24 (Box Box 376)
      - Joint Committee on Reduction of Non essential Federal Expenditures, 1954 January 13 (Box Box 376)
      - Radio - (Campaign Speech), Richmond, Virginia, 1952 July 14 (Box Box 376)
      - Virginia Democratic Convention, Roanoke, Va., 1952 July 17 (Box Box 376)
      - American Legion, Department of Virginia, Richmond, Virginia, 1952 August 8 (Box Box 376)
      - Radio Speech from Winchester, Virginia, 1952 October 17 (Box Box 376)
      - National Retail Dry Goods Association, New York, 1953 January 15 (Box Box 376)
      - Radio transcription for Gannett News Service in Washington, D. C., 1953 January 16 (Box Box 376)
      - Remarks in the Senate on the Charles E. Wilson nomination, 1953 January 26 (Box Box 376)
      - Remarks at the Alfalfa Club, 1953 January 31 (Box Box 376)
      - Material for Harkness interview, 1953 February 19 (Box Box 376)
      - Remarks on receiving an award from the American Good Government Society, Washington, D.C., 1953 February 23 (Box Box 376)
      - The Federal Budget, Lexington, Virginia, 1953 March 8 (Box Box 376)
      - Remarks at Portsmouth, Virginia, 1953 April 22 (Box Box 376)
      - Statement in the Senate on the Byrd Budget, 1953 April 25 (Box Box 376)
      - U. S. Chamber of Commerce, Washington, D. C., 1953 April 27 (Box Box 376)
      - Senate - Complimenting Senator Margaret Chase Smith, 1953 May 27 (Box Box 377)
      - Remarks in the Senate on the RFC and a Small Business Administration, 1953 June 22 (Box Box 377)
      - Extension of remarks in the Senate Tightening the Federal Purse Strings, 1953 June 22 (Box Box 377)
      - Report of Joint Committee relating to control of collection and use of foreign currencies, 1953 June 23 (Box Box 377)
      - Remarks in the Senate on fiscal situation, 1953 June 24 (Box Box 377)
      - Senate - St. Lawrence Seaway, 1954 January 20 (Box Box 377)
      - Chamber of Commerce, Little Rock, Ark., 1954 January 21 (Box Box 377)
      - Alfalfa Club Dinner, 1954 January 23 (Box Box 377)
      - Civil employment in Executive branch and Unexpended balances of Federal Appropriations, 1954 February 3 (Box Box 377)
      - Sons of the American Revolution, Newark, N. J., 1954 February 22 (Box Box 377)
      - American Good Government Society, 1954 February 22 (Box Box 377)
      - Byrd Budget Recommendations, 1954 March 8 (Box Box 377)
      - Civilian Employment in Executive Branch, 1954 March 10 (Box Box 377)
      - Remarks in the Senate on the Tax Legislation, when Senator Byrd and Senator Williams offered an amendment., 1954 March 25 (Box Box 377)
      - Remarks in the Senate on the Tax Bill. HR 8324, 1954 March 30 (Box Box 377)
      - Remarks in the Senate paying tribute to Senator Johnson of Colorado, 1954 April 6 (Box Box 377)
      - Remarks in the Senate on the construction of certain public buildings. HR 6342, 1954 April 8 (Box Box 377)
      - Remarks in the Senate on the Federal Housing Administration, 1954 April 14 (Box Box 377)
      - Remarks in the Senate on H.R.6342, Con struction of Public Buildings by Purchase Contracts, 1954 April 15 (Box Box 377)
      - Senate - Lease-Purchase Bill, 1954 April 20 (Box Box 377)
      - Unexpended balances of Federal Appropriations, 1954 May 3 (Box Box 377)
      - Remarks and letters in the Congressional Record relating to Federal Housing Administration, 1954 May 3 (Box Box 377)
      - National Association of Plumbing Con tractors, Washington, D. C., 1954 May 10 (Box Box 377)
      - Farm-City Conference, New York, N. Y., 1954 May 25 (Box Box 377)
      - Remarks in the Senate on the death of Senator Hoey, 1954 May 27 (Box Box 377)
      - Senate - Federal Housing Program, 1954 June 15 (Box Box 378)
      - Senate - Unexpended Balances, 1954 June 16 (Box Box 378)
      - Remarks in the Senate in regard to defense appropriations, 1954 June 18 (Box Box 378)
      - Council for Community Improvement, Washington, D. C., 1954 June 24 (Box Box 378)
      - Remarks in the Senate on Public Housing Programs, 1954 June 25 (Box Box 378)
      - Senate - Funds Received From Germany, 1954 June 25 (Box Box 378)
      - Senate - Federal Housing Program, 1954 June 30 (Box Box 378)
      - Purchasing Power of the Dollar. (Not delivered), 1954 June 30 (Box Box 378)
      - Tax Bill. (Not delivered), 1954 June 30 (Box Box 378)
      - Senate - Tax Bill, 1954 July 1 (Box Box 378)
      - Senate - Tax Bill, 1954 July 2 (Box Box 378)
      - Civilian employment in Executive Branch, May 1954, 1954 July 7 (Box Box 378)
      - Senate - Byrd-Bridges Amendment, S.J. Res. 174, 1954 July 13 (Box Box 378)
      - Housing Bill, 1954 July 22 (Box Box 378)
      - Senate - Discussion on the Housing Bill, 1954 July 28 (Box Box 378)
      - Senate - Mutual Security Act, 1954 July 29 (Box Box 378)
      - Remarks in the Senate, 1954 August 2 (Box Box 378)
      - Letter from Senator Byrd to Hon. Albert M. Cole of FHA, 1954 August 6 (Box Box 378)
      - Senate - Debt Limit, 1954 August 13 (Box Box 378)
      - Senate - Remarks on R.E.A., 1954 August 13 (Box Box 378)
      - Senate - Temporary Increase in the Federal Debt Limit, 1954 August 13 (Box Box 378)
      - Remarks at Senator's 33rd. Picnic, 1954 August 28 (Box Box 378)
      - Memorial Address in the Senate for Senator Maybank. (Folder empty when processed), 1954 November 9 (Box Box 378)
      - Memorial Address for Senator Butler of Nebraska, 1954 November 9 (Box Box 378)
      - Memorial Address in the Senate for Senator McCarran, 1954 November 9 (Box Box 378)
      - Federal personnel, June-September 1954, 1954 November 16 (Box Box 378)
      - Houston Speech, [1954?] (Box Box 378)
      - Remarks in offering amendment to Sec. 7237 of the Internal Revenue Code of 1954, 1955 January 18 (Box Box 378)
      - Remarks in paying tribute to U. S. Junior Chamber of Commerce and Virginia Junior Chamber of Commerce, 1955 January 21 (Box Box 378)
      - Virginia State Horticulture Society, Roanoke, Virginia, 1955 January 25 (Box Box 378)
      - Senate - Formosa situation, 1955 January 28 (Box Box 378)
      - Senate - Unexpended Balances in Executive Agencies, 1955 February 1 (Box Box 378)
      - Report of Joint Committee on Reduction of Nonessential Federal Expenditures on Federal Personnel, 1955 February 4 (Box Box 378)
      - The Atlanta Freight Bureau, Atlanta, Ga., 1955 February 18 (Box Box 378)
      - Remarks in the Senate - Clay Road Program, 1955 March 2 (Box Box 378)
      - Tax Bill. (Folder empty when processed), 1955 March 2 (Box Box 378)
      - Senate - Federal Highway Plan, 1955 March 10 (Box Box 378)
      - Senate - Tax Bill H.R. 4259, 1955 March 10 (Box Box 378)
      - Senate - Proposed Federal Tax Legislation. (Folder empty when processed), 1955 March 11 (Box Box 378)
      - Remarks in the Senate in connection with the tax bill, 1955 March 14 (Box Box 378)
      - Senate - Tax Legislation, 1955 March 14 (Box Box 378)
      - Remarks in the Senate on the tax bill. (Folder empty when processed), 1955 March 15 (Box Box 378)
      - Remarks in the Senate on appointment of conferees for the Tax Bill, 1955 March 16 (Box Box 378)